cdbank.co.il 2013-06-30

# Webstockpro - Privacy Policy

Webstockpro - Privacy Policy   
Webstockpro respects your privacy and takes the responsibility of protecting the information that you provide to us seriously. This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information.   
Our goal is to provide you with the best user experience possible. The information you provide helps us enhance and improve our service for the benefit of you and our other customers.   
By using this website you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.   
Information Collection   
**Personal information:** When you create or update your Webstockpro account, or when you make a purchase on our website, you voluntarily provide us the following personal information: your name, company name, mailing address, email address, password and phone number. We provide you with tools to access and modify the personal information you provided to us and is associated with your account. If you need assistance in accessing, updating or deleting your personal information, you may contact us at support@webstockpro.com.   
**Non-personal information:** We use a variety of third party services such as Google Analytics to help us understand the usage of our service. These services may collect non-personal information sent by your browser.   
**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookies" (a cookie is a small file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk) to help provide you with a continuous surfing experience.   
**Transaction Information:** We use an outside credit card processing company to bill our customers. When you place an order on our site we do not store your credit card information.   
Information usage and sharing   
We will never sell your personal information to a third party without your permission.   
We will not send you unsolicited emails except for site wide announcements, or specific notifications that are delivered directly to your account.   
When you make a purchase on our website, we are required to provide some of your contact and order information to the publishers of our licensed content. However, no financial information is provided to the publishers except for the total license price.   
We may disclose your information in order to comply with legal requirements and obligations.   
Security   
We store your information on secure servers and restrict access to these servers. We use encryption, firewalls, and other methods to keep you information safe.   
We limit access to your personal information only to specific employees who provide customer service functions.   
Your account information is password-protected. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential, and we encourage you to change your password from time to time. If you lose your password, we will help you recover it after verifying your identity.   
Payments are processed via PayPal using SSL encryption technology. We do not retain credit card information on our servers.   
Changes to this Policy   
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes, we update the "last updated" date at the bottom of this page.   
We welcome your questions and comments. If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.   
This Privacy Policy was last updated on February 1st, 2011.   
  
All rights reserved. © 1993-2013
